Guide to the Kevin Killian and Dodie Bellamy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Research files, 1977-2009; Series IV; 8.88; (9 boxes)
  - Research on Jack Spicer
    - Research Files
      - Blackburn, Paul, 1965 August 17 (Box 42)
      - Blaser, Robin, 1990-2003, undated; 10 (Box 42)
        - To Donald Allen, 1959; 1991 (Box 42)
        - Tributes on his 70th birthday solicited by Kevin Killian, 1995, undated (Box 42)
        - The Recovery of the Public World conference 1995, 1995, undated (Box 42)
        - Letters to Duncan, 1960-1965, undated (Box 42)
        - Robin Blaser and Charles Olson, 1995 June (Box 42)
        - 3 Evenings in Provence, 1995 (Box 42)
        - Blaser/Spicer, "A Semperealistic Poem for Jo Miles", undated (Box 42)
        - Pretty Please, undated (Box 42)
      - Borregaard, Ebbe /Robert Duncan quarrel, 1961, undated (Box 42)
      - Bottone, Gary (Jack Spicer in Minneapolis, negative) [photo], undated (Box 42)
      - Boundary II Spicer materials, 1977 Fall (Box 42)
      - Bowerings, George, 1996-2007, undated; 4 (Box 42)
      - Bowker, Kent, 1998-2001, undated; 4 (Box 42)
        - Spicer/Cafe negative [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - Spicer/beach negative [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - Car Photo negative [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - Spicer/Duncan/bed negative [photo], 1998, undated (Box 42)
      - Boyd, Bruce (materials), 1990, undated (Box 42)
      - Brautigan, Richard (materials), 1990, undated (Box 42)
      - Brito, Manuel, 1992, undated; 2 (Box 42)
      - Brockway, Lyn, 1990 December 31 (Box 42)
      - Broderick, John (SUN SPOTS from Bancroft Spicer papers), 1965, undated (Box 42)
      - Brodwcky, Bill, 2013 December 18 (Box 42)
      - Bromige, David, 1990, undated (Box 42)
        - Interview in ARSHILE, undated (Box 42)
      - Broughton, James, 1988-1999, undated; 6 (Box 42)
      - Brower, David, 1991 February 04 (Box 43)
      - Brown University (Eigner Lorca), 1958, undated (Box 43)
      - Burns, Wayne, 1991 August 13 (Box 43)
      - Burton, Hilda, 1991 (Box 43)
      - Button, John (to Robin Blaser 1961) (Box 43)
      - California Librarian, 1970 October (Box 43)
      - Cerruti, Laura, 2007 November 05 (Box 43)
      - Chicago Review, 1997, undated (Box 43)
      - Chugg, Gail, 1991 July 07 (Box 43)
      - Spicer/Chugg, Questions about Heads of the Town, undated (Box 43)
      - Coleman, Victor, 1996 December 16 (Box 43)
      - Collapse material, undated (Box 43)
      - Collected Jack Spicer (Readers Reports for new CJS), 2007, undated (Box 43)
      - Columbia University Press, 1993 (Box 43)
      - Conjunctions, 1992, undated (Box 43)
      - Corman, Cid, 1990 (Box 43)
      - Creeley, Robert, 1991-1998, undated; 3 (Box 43)
      - Robert Creeley/Jack Spicer, 1955, undated (Box 43)
      - Kevin Ray (Creeley's Letters to Spicer), 1991 May 15 (Box 43)
      - Davidson, Michael, 1994, undated (Box 43)
      - Day, Wesley, 1991–1992 (Box 43)
      - DeBeck, Brian, 2008 January 31 (Box 43)
      - Delany, Samuel R., 1997 (Box 43)
      - De Gruttola, Raffael, 1991-1992, undated; 3 (Box 43)
      - de Thassy, Eugene to Blaser and Spicer, Dec 1955, 1955 December (Box 43)
      - Devlin, James, 1990 November 09 (Box 43)
      - Diaman, NA, 1984–1997 (Box 43)
      - Diamant, Steve, 1957-1997, undated (Box 43)
      - Drew House, Stinson Beach [photo], undated (Box 43)
      - Dull, Harold, 1964 (Box 43)
      - Duncan, Robert (Box 43)
        - Letters, 1958 (Box 43)
        - Duncan/Witt-Diamant quarrels, 1991 (Box 43)
        - Sex Map of 2029, undated (Box 43)
        - Robert Duncan writing, 1952, undated (Box 43)
        - Letters to Blaser, 1956–1963 (Box 43)
        - Robert Duncan as Visual Artist (Mythos Gallery Panel), undated (Box 43)
        - Spicer and Medieval Scenes MS., 1962; 1991 (Box 43)
        - University Art Museum [Duncan show], 1991, undated (Box 43)
      - Dunn, Joe, 1990-1996, undated (Box 43)
      - DuPlessis, Rachel Blau, 1990, undated (Box 43)
      - Edwards, Ernie, 1997-1999, undated; 2 (Box 43)
      - Eigner, Larry, 1990 November 17 (Box 43)
      - Eisenberg, Jeremy, 2009, undated (Box 43)
      - Ellingham, Lew, 1985-2007, undated; 6 (Box 43)
        - Register of Ellingham Papers, 1983–1987 (Box 43)
        - Ellingham's Review of Blaser's Syntax, undated (Box 43)
      - Ellis, Merle, 1990 November 01 (Box 43)
      - Everson, Landis, 1951; 1990; 3 (Box 43)
        - Landis Everson to Robin Blaser 2004 (Box 43)
        - Landis Everson to Blaser 1 9 5 6 (Box 43)
        - Landis Everson to Jack Spicer, undated (Box 43)
        - Landis Everson Poems, 2004, undated (Box 43)
        - Landis Everson to Josephine Miles, undated (Box 43)
      - Fabian, Gerald, 1998-2003, undated (Box 43)
      - Fabian photo of Holy Grail dinner [photo and negative], undated (Box 43)
      - Faggot Vomit Poetry Project Newsletter 1997 (Box 43)
      - Fagin, Larry, 1998-2003, undated (Box 43)
      - Farwell, David, undated (Box 43)
      - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1990; 1996 (Box 43)
        - Ferlinghetti Interview, undated (Box 43)
      - Fernandez, Vince, 1997–1998 (Box 43)
      - Field, Tom, 1992-1997, undated (Box 43)
        - Tom Field, photo of Kyger and Jacobus, undated (Box 43)
      - Fitzgerald, Dora, 1985-1993, undated; 3 (Box 43)
        - Dora Fitzgerald to Joanne Kyger, 1960–1962 (Box 43)
        - Dora Fitzgerald Dulls negative [photo], undated (Box 43)
        - Dora and Russell after elopement negative and print [photo], undated (Box 43)
        - Dora ... with twins ... negative and print [photo], undated (Box 43)
        - George and Bill in garden by Dora [photo], undated (Box 43)
        - Russell FitzGerald as a teen ... negative [photo], undated (Box 43)
        - Dora's photos, Lew jitterbugging Negative and print [photo], undated (Box 43)
      - Fitzgerald, Russell, 1957, undated; 2 (Box 43)
        - Russell Fitzgerald Diary, 1996, undated (Box 43)
        - Russell Fitzgerald Works, 1985, undated (Box 43)
        - Russell Fitzgerald Archive Inventory, undated (Box 43)
        - Lost photo of Russell (from ACTS), undated (Box 43)
      - Foot Magazine Letter, 1990, undated (Box 43)
      - Foote, Gilbert "TIM", 1993, undated (Box 43)
      - Foster, Ed, 1997 (Box 43)
      - Foutu, Faust, 1991 (Box 43)
      - Fraser, Simon (INVENTORY OF TAPES), undated (Box 43)
      - Frazer, Len, 1998, undated (Box 43)
      - Fredman, Stephen, 2008 (Box 43)
      - Frost, Nemi, 1997, undated (Box 43)
        - Nemi, George, Bill etc. at beach house (negative and print) [photo], undated (Box 43)
      - Fyffe, Richard, 1992 (Box 43)
      - Gay and Lesbian Literature (Jack Spicer Entry), 1993-1997, undated; 2 (Box 43)
      - Gilbert, Jack, 1966; 1990 (Box 43)
      - Jack Gilbert, Magic Workshop Questionnaire, undated (Box 43)
      - Gilmore, Lyman, 1994-1997, undated (Box 43)
      - Ginsberg, Allen, undated (Box 43)
      - Gizzi, Peter, 1992, undated (Box 43)
      - Gleason, Madeline (Papers), 1959-1979, undated (Box 43)
      - Golden, Mertis to Joanne Kyger, 1960 (Box 43)
      - Goldwasser, Thomas (Jack Spicer offerings Oct 2012), undated (Box 43)
      - Gnostic, undated (Box 43)
      - Goldstein, Mark, 2008-2009, undated (Box 43)
      - Goodwin, JF, 1982-1987, undated (Box 43)
      - Grand Street, 1998, undated (Box 43)
      - Hacker, Marilyn, 1992, undated (Box 43)
      - Haimsohn, George, undated (Box 43)
      - Halverson, John, 1997 (Box 43)
      - Hardwick, Bonnie, 1990, undated (Box 43)
      - Harmon, Harvey, undated (Box 43)
      - Harris, Latif, undated (Box 43)
      - Hart, Lawrence, 1996 June 06 (Box 43)
      - Harter, Christopher (J Magazine Problem), undated (Box 43)
      - Harwood, Lee, 1990-1991, undated (Box 43)
      - Herndon, Fran, 1997-2011, undated (Box 43)
        - Fran Herndon, photo 1957 +negative [photo], undated (Box 43)
      - Herndon, Jim, undated (Box 43)
        - Photo Negative [photo], undated (Box 43)
      - Hindmarch, Gladys, 1991 July 10 (Box 43)
      - Hodes, Ida, 1988-1991, undated (Box 43)
      - Hogan, William (SF Chronicle, 1960) (Box 43)
      - Howard, Peter [photo], undated (Box 43)
      - Hull, David, undated (Box 43)
      - Hutchinson, Paul, 1997, undated (Box 43)
      - The Impercipient Lecture Series, 1997 September (Box 44)
      - Independent Curators International (ICI Jess Exhibition), 2006-2007, undated (Box 44)
      - Jacobus, Harry, undated (Box 44)
      - Jess, 1990-2009, undated; 3 (Box 44)
      - Jess Collins family, 2004 (Box 44)
      - Jonas, Steve, 1965, undated (Box 44)
      - Joyce, Allen (letters), 1955–1956 (Box 44)
      - Katz, Daniel (Beat Scene Jack Spicer), undated (Box 44)
      - Kearney, Larry, 1996, undated; 2 (Box 44)
        - Larry Kearney, letter to Jack Spicer, undated (Box 44)
        - Larry Kearney, "North Beach", undated (Box 44)
      - Keilty, James, 1998, undated (Box 44)
      - Kelly, Robert, 1996 (Box 44)
      - Kerouac, Jack 1960 photo [photo] (Box 44)
      - Kerouac, Jack to Donald Allen, 1959-1962, undated (Box 44)
      - Kidd, Walter E. (materials), 1956–1990 (Box 44)
      - King, Basil, 1992 (Box 44)
      - Korte, Mary Norbert, 1990–1991 (Box 44)
      - Krech, Richard, 2006, undated (Box 44)
      - Krikorian, Leo, undated (Box 44)
      - Kyger, Joanne, 1959–1998 (Box 44)
        - Joanne Kyger to Gary Snyder, 1959, undated (Box 44)
        - Joanne Kyger to Michael Rumaker, 1958 (Box 44)
        - Kyger, negative, Jess, Ebbe, Spicer [photo], undated (Box 44)
        - Joanne Kyger/ Tom Field negative [photo], 1959, undated (Box 44)
      - Langan, John Gibbons, 1992 (Box 44)
      - Lansing, Gerrit, 1990-1991, undated; 2 (Box 44)
      - Laughlin, James, 1997 January 08 (Box 44)
      - Lennon, Bobby/ Barbara Nicholls (Photograph of Spicer's friend) [photo], undated (Box 44)
      - Lerman, Jose Ramon, 1999 (Box 44)
      - LeSueur, Joe, 1997 (Box 44)
      - Levertov, Denise, 1997 December 23 (Box 44)
      - Lewis, Glenn, 1990–1991 (Box 44)
      - Liddy, James, 1997, undated; 2 (Box 44)
      - Lilly Library, 1991, undated (Box 44)
      - Livesay, Dorothy, 1991, undated (Box 44)
      - Dorothy Livesay / Renee Rodin, 1991, undated (Box 44)
      - Loewinsohn, Ron to Joanne Kyger, 1963 June 02 (Box 44)
      - Lowell, Robert (materials), 1959; 1990 (Box 44)
      - Ludwar, Terry, 1990-1991, undated (Box 44)
      - Mackintosh, Graham, undated (Box 44)
        - "Oliver Charms" letter, undated (Box 44)
        - Letters, 1954-1955, undated (Box 44)
      - Mallman, Jerome, undated (Box 44)
      - Map Research, 2004, undated (Box 44)
      - Martin, Fred, 1997 February 17 (Box 44)
      - Mattachine materials (from SF Gay Lesbian History Museum), 1953, undated (Box 44)
      - Maud, Ralph, 1996 December 30 (Box 44)
      - Maynard, John Arthur, 1996 December (Box 44)
      - Mazer, Ben, 2004 March 12 (Box 44)
      - Premier of Spicer's YOUNG GOODMAN BROWN 10/29/05 [photo], undated (Box 44)
      - McClure, Michael, 1992-2000, undated; 3 (Box 44)
      - McGrath, Earl, 1991 (Box 44)
      - McWilliam, Eileen, 1995-1997, undated (Box 44)
      - Michigan State Library, 1991 August 12 (Box 44)
      - Miller, Bett, 1991–1992 (Box 44)
      - Montague, John (The Pear Is Ripe), 2007; 2 (Box 44)
      - Moore, Alvin William ("Pacific Transport"), 1996 (Box 44)
      - Moore, Marianne, 1990–1997 (Box 44)
      - Moore, Mary, 2000-2001, undated (Box 44)
      - Morehart, Mart, 1997 August 13 (Box 44)
        - The Morehart Hoax (from BED), undated (Box 44)
        - Jack Spicer and Friends [photo], undated (Box 44)
      - Motokiyu, Tosa, 1992, undated; 2 (Box 44)
      - Mullholland, Kate, undated (Box 44)
      - Nest Article, 2004; 2 (Box 44)
      - Neumeyer, Peter F., 1999-2011, undated (Box 44)
      - Neville, Tove (Negative of Spicer Sister Korte) [photo], undated (Box 44)
      - New York Public Library, 1997 (Box 44)
      - Nicholls, Barbara, 2002-2009, undated; 5 (Box 44)
        - Spicer [photo], undated (Box 44)
      - Nichols, Miriam, 1997 March 20 (Box 44)
      - Norton, Linda, undated (Box 44)
      - O Blek (Spicer material), undated (Box 44)
      - Oliveros, Pauline, 1996 December 16 (Box 44)
      - Olson, Charles, undated (Box 44)
        - Charles Olson/ Jack Spicer, undated (Box 44)
        - To Lew Ellingham, undated (Box 44)
      - "Once on Maiden Lane" (to be identified), 1960 (Box 44)
      - Onderwyzer, Gaby Stuart, 1993 (Box 44)
      - Parkinson, Ariel, 1991-1998, undated; 2 (Box 44)
        - Letter to Blaser regarding Dictation and Yeats, 1970 October 11 (Box 44)
        - On Olson and Spicer, 1985; 1995 (Box 44)
        - Negatives [photo], undated (Box 44)
      - Parkinson, Thomas, 1991-1997, undated (Box 44)
      - Patchen, Kenneth (materials), 1961; 1990 (Box 44)
      - PBA Galleries, 2008 (Box 44)
      - Peacock Gallery, 1955; 1990 (Box 44)
      - Pearce, Roy Harvey papers, 1968; 1996 (Box 44)
      - Persky, Stan, 1990-1999, undated; 2 (Box 44)
        - Article on Blaser, undated (Box 44)
      - Pettitt, Kenneth, 1956; 1992 (Box 44)
        - [Poet Be Like God] (Box 45)
        - Reviews, 1998-1999, undated (Box 45)
        - Royalties, 1998 April 30 (Box 45)
      - Poetry (Jack Spicer, reviewed in Poetry), 2008 (Box 45)
      - "Poetry" magazine proofs, undated (Box 45)
      - Poetry as Magic Workshop, undated; 2 (Box 45)
      - Poetry Center (Box 45)
        - Permissions, 1990 (Box 45)
      - Porter, Bern, 1997 (Box 45)
      - Prevallet, Kristin, 1999 June (Box 45)
      - Publishers Weekly, 1998, undated (Box 45)
      - Rago, Henry (Letter), 1965 June 03 (Box 45)
      - Random House (Frank O'Hara), 1997 October (Box 45)
      - Redl, Harry, 1997 (Box 45)
        - Spicer and negatives [photo], undated (Box 45)
        - Magic Workshop negative print (Kostalefsky, Borregaard, door, Duncan) [photo], undated (Box 45)
        - Magic Workshop 2, negative [photo], undated (Box 45)
        - Spicer photo (negative) [photo], undated (Box 45)
        - Jack Spicer and others [photo], undated (Box 45)
      - Rexroth, Kenneth, 1965 June (Box 45)
      - Rickman, Gregg, 1991, undated (Box 45)
      - Riley, Peter, 1991 (Box 45)
      - RLIN Search for Jack Spicer, undated (Box 45)
      - Roberts, Jim to Jack Spicer, 1949 June 22 (Box 45)
        (envelope only)
      - Rodin, Renee, 1991 (Box 45)
      - Rummonds, Richard, 1991-1997, undated (Box 45)
      - Ryan, John Allen, 1994, undated; 2 (Box 45)
      - Sagetrieb (Proofs of Blaser article for Sagetrieb), 2000, undated (Box 45)
      - SF Art Institute, circa 1954 (Box 45)
      - Sattler, Martha, 1990 (Box 45)
      - Scheiner, Betsey (PBLG edits), 1996, undated (Box 45)
      - Schevill, James, 1992 (Box 45)
      - Schiff, Harris, 1990–1991 (Box 45)
      - Sears (Behind the Mask of the Mattachine), undated (Box 45)
      - Selwyn, Herb, undated (Box 45)
      - Simon Fraser University (Box 45)
        - Jess Papers, 1967, undated (Box 45)
        - Spicer Papers, undated (Box 45)
      - Six Gallery, undated (Box 45)
      - Smith, Rod, AERIAL (Journal), 1992-2015, undated (Box 45)
      - Snyder, Gary, 1993–1997 (Box 45)
      - Spangler, Janet, 1997 October 10 (Box 45)
      - Spicer Conference, 1986, undated (Box 45)
      - Spicer Permissions, undated; 2 (Box 45)
      - Spicer, Dorothy to Blaser after Jack's funeral August 1965 (Box 45)
      - Stanley, George, 1990-2002, undated; 3 (Box 45)
        - George Stanley to Robin Blaser Dec 7, 1961, 1961 December 07 (Box 45)
      - Starr, Leslie (Wesleyan), 2007 November 08 (Box 45)
      - SUNY Stony Brook 1991, 1991 February 04 (Box 45)
      - Stewart, Josephine Fredman, 1992, undated (Box 45)
      - Tagett, Richard, 1991-2000, undated (Box 45)
      - Tallman, Ellen, 1991-1992, undated (Box 45)
      - Tallman, Karen, 1991 (Box 45)
        - Jack Spicer [photo], undated (Box 45)
      - Tejada, Roberto (Spicer in Spanish), 1996 December 25 (Box 45)
      - TO Interview, 1994 (Box 45)
      - Todd, Glenn, 2004 January 15 (Box 45)
      - Torra, Joseph, 1992, undated (Box 45)
      - Tovery, Eloise (Interview with Duncan), 1995, undated (Box 45)
      - Townsend, Jim, 1991, undated (Box 45)
      - Turnbull, Gael, 1999 November 24 (Box 45)
      - Turner, Eloise (Mixon), 1990, undated (Box 45)
      - Tysh, George, 1990 October 25 (Box 45)
      - SUNY Buffalo, 1990-2009, undated; 3 (Box 45)
      - UCLA, 1990-1992, undated (Box 45)
      - UCSD, 1966–1997; 2 (Box 45)
      - University of Connecticut, 1990-1991, undated (Box 45)
      - Vincent, Stephen, 1948–1992 (Box 45)
      - Wagstaff, Chirstopher, 1998-2006, undated (Box 45)
        - An Opening of the Field, 2012, undated (Box 45)
      - Wah, Fred, 1996 (Box 45)
      - Wakoski, Diane, 1997, undated (Box 45)
      - Warner, John Francis, 1987-2004, undated; 2 (Box 45)
        - Golden Days in North Beach, undated (Box 45)
      - Washington University, 1991, undated; 2 (Box 45)
      - Watson, Scott, 1991–1992 (Box 45)
      - Wesleyan University Press, 1997-2008, undated; 2 (Box 45)
        - Jack Spicer, Collected Poems contract, 2008 (Box 45)
      - Whalen, Philip, 1997 (Box 45)
        - To Joanne Kyger, undated (Box 45)
      - What Sticks to the Real, 2009 December (Box 45)
      - White Rabbit Press Catalogue, undated (Box 45)
      - Wieners, John (materials), 1959, undated (Box 45)
        - John Wieners to Robin Blaser 1997, 1997, undated (Box 45)
        - John Wieners to Blaser Nov 7 1956?, circa 1956 (Box 45)
      - Williams, Jonathan, 1990-1998, undated; 2 (Box 45)
      - Willis, Patricia, 1997 March 20 (Box 45)
      - Witt-Diamant, Ruth, 1960; 1990 (Box 45)
      - Wixman, Myrsam (Letters), 1955–1956 (Box 45)
      - Wolf, Leonard, undated (Box 45)
      - Writers Conference Spring Poetry Festival Program, undated (Box 45)
      - Zaslove, Jerry, 1991 (Box 45)
    - Poems and manuscripts [transcriptions]
      - Admonitions (original), undated (Box 46)
      - An Answer to Jaime D 'Angulo, undated (Box 46)
      - Antique Scenes, undated (Box 46)
      - Armed with Madness (Mary Butts' ARMED WITH MADNESS dramatized by Jack Spicer), undated (Box 46)
      - Bed (Flaming Tales of True Romance), undated (Box 46)
      - Billy the Kid, undated (Box 46)
      - Bing Buddha sings, undated (Box 46)
      - Black swan fragment, undated (Box 46)
      - Buster Keaton's Shadow, undated (Box 46)
      - A Canto for Ezra Pound, undated (Box 46)
      - A Clean Break, undated (Box 46)
      - The Clouds, undated (Box 46)
      - Coffee Time, undated (Box 46)
      - Cross Word fragment, undated (Box 46)
      - Dear Ferlinghetti, undated (Box 46)
      - Death By Water, undated (Box 46)
      - Dialogue between Intellect Passion aka Dialogue on Love between two future lovers, undated (Box 46)
      - Dick Stone, 1955, undated (Box 46)
      - Dillinger, undated (Box 46)
      - Fugitive poem from Blue Canary, 2003 (Box 46)
      - Gentle Warning, 1956 (Box 46)
      - George Stanley, 1958 (Box 46)
      - George Sterling, undated (Box 46)
      - Golem Galleys, undated (Box 46)
      - Graveyard play, undated (Box 46)
      - Greasewood, Ridiculous, Ask the right question, and detective novel cross-out, undated (Box 46)
      - Hospital Scenes I, undated (Box 46)
      - How's Your Ghost?, undated (Box 46)
      - Imaginary Elegies, 1992, undated (Box 46)
      - Intemperance, undated (Box 46)
      - LAMP, undated (Box 46)
      - Letters to Lorca, undated (Box 46)
      - Map Poems, 2006, undated; 4 (Box 46)
      - A New Poem, undated (Box 46)
      - No daring shadows, undated (Box 46)
      - Orpheus in Athens, undated (Box 46)
      - Minnesota fragments, undated (Box 46)
      - A New Testament (with note by Spicer to Peter Shoemaker), 1968, undated (Box 46)
      - One Night Stand (poem with corrections), undated (Box 46)
      - Orpheus (prose fragment), undated (Box 46)
      - A Play of Five Tragedies, undated (Box 46)
      - A Pook-Up for Robin Blaser, 1956 (Box 46)
      - Portrait of the Artist as a Young Landscape (Buffalo), undated; 3 (Box 46)
      - Prose, 1956 (Box 46)
      - The Prostitute and The Scholar, undated (Box 46)
      - Protocols of the Elders of Unwisdom, undated (Box 46)
      - Quick, Said the Bird, undated; 3 (Box 46)
      - Re A Poem for Josephine Miles, undated (Box 46)
      - The Red Wheelbarrow, 1995, undated; 2 (Box 46)
      - Romance Sonambulo, 2004, undated (Box 46)
      - Satire of New Criticism, undated (Box 46)
      - A Second Train Song for Gary, undated (Box 46)
      - September Song, undated (Box 46)
      - Socrates, undated (Box 46)
      - Sonnet for Gary / Sonnet for the Beginning of Winter, undated (Box 46)
      - the spicer / ferlinghetti correspondence (White Rabbit Broadside), undated (Box 46)
      - Spider Song, undated (Box 46)
      - There is a road somewhere, undated (Box 46)
      - Tower of Babel, 1963, undated (Box 46)
      - Troilus, 1955, undated; 3 (Box 46)
      - The Wasps, undated (Box 46)
      - Young Goodman Brown, undated (Box 46)
      - [ZERO], undated (Box 46)
      - Unidentified, undated; 2 (Box 46)
      - List of works by Killian, undated (Box 46)
      - Jean Cocteau, "On Memory" (translated by Alec Brown), undated (Box 46)
      - Billy the Kid Musical, 2014, undated (Box 46)
      - Russell Fitzgerald Tarot deck, undated (Box 46)
      - Spicer Shadows Contract, 2014, undated (Box 46)
      - Jack Spicer, Riddle #1 and #2 Answered with guesses, undated (Box 46)
      - Jack Spicer letters to Myrsam Wixman ed. By Bruce Boone, undated (Box 46)
      - Jack Spicer and David Schaff 1965 Scholarly Detective Work by Daniel Benjamin, 2014, undated (Box 46)
      - Jack Spicer letter to David Schaff, 2014 (Box 46)
      - Lewis DeForest Brown, 2014, undated (Box 46)
    - Correspondence
      - Allen, Donald, 1957-1991, undated; 4 (Box 46)
      - Blaser, Robin, 1950–1958 (Box 46)
      - Blaser, Robin and Eileen Fitzgerald, undated (Box 46)
      - Boston Newsletter, undated (Box 46)
      - Duncan, Robert, 1946-1995, undated; 3 (Box 46)
      - Jess, circa 1959 (Box 46)
      - Minneapolis Letters, 1950-1965, undated (Box 46)
      - Miscellaneous Added Letters, 1959-1994, undated (Box 46)
      - Olson, Charles, 1991, undated; 2 (Box 46)
      - Rago, Henry, undated (Box 46)
      - San Quentin feeler 1958, 1958, undated (Box 46)
      - Schiff, Harris, 1963; 1997 (Box 46)
      - Tallman, Ellen Warren, 1965; 2002 (Box 46)
      - Williams, Jonathan, 1955, undated (Box 46)
    - Papers and notes
      - From After Lorca notebooks, undated (Box 46)
      - Bancroft Library, 2004, undated (Box 46)
      - Beatitude annotated by J. Spicer 1959 (Box 46)
      - Berkeley Notebook Ten, undated (Box 46)
      - Chronology, undated (Box 46)
      - Donne's Use of Medieval Geographical Lore, English 199 (Box 46)
      - Emerson Notes, 2004, undated (Box 46)
      - History of a Historian (Spicer's Uncle), 1956 February (Box 46)
      - Magic Workshop Questionnaires, undated (Box 46)
      - Notes on Duncan's HD book?, undated (Box 46)
      - Pages from Language notebook (at Simon Fraser Univ.), undated (Box 46)
      - Pentheus Notebook, undated (Box 46)
      - Spicer Boxes, Monday, May 24, 2004, undated (Box 46)
      - Spicer Boxes, Tuesday, May 25, 2004, undated (Box 46)
      - Spicer Boxes, Wednesday, May 26, 2004, undated (Box 46)
      - Spicer Boxes, Thursday, May 27, 2004, undated (Box 46)
      - Stanford, 1981-1992, undated (Box 46)
      - University of Texas, Austin (Spicer Papers), 1995, undated (Box 46)
    - Photos (uncredited)
      - Jack Spicer (Yearbook?) [photo], undated (Box 46)
      - Spicer at Berkeley conference (negative and print) [photo], 1965 (Box 46)
      - Sunday afternoon workshop, print [photo], undated (Box 46)